Dell H. Hymes Papers 1947-1992 Mss.Ms.Coll.55
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1951-1987; 17 lin. feet (Box 1-32)
  - Frank, Delbert, 1986
  - Frank, Russell, 1983-1984
  - Franklin, J. A., 1954
  - Franklin, Karl, 1968
  - Frantz, Charles, 1983-1985
  - The Free Press, 1978,1986
  - Freedle, Roy, 1982
  - Freeman, John & Elsie, 1964-1965
  - Freilich, Morris, 1979
  - French, David H., 1953-1981
  - Freund, Hugo, 1981-1982
  - Friedl, Ernestine, 1981,1985-1986
  - Friedrich, Paul, 1957-1975,1982-1987
  - Frisch, Michael, 1983
  - Fromm, Erich, 1973
  - Fuchs, Anna, 1964
  - G. and C. Merriam Company, 1957-1960
  - Ganguly, P. G., 1969
  - Gardin, Jean-Claude, 1962-1965,1975
  - Gardner, Carol, 1971-1975
  - Garfinkel, Harold, 1965-1971
  - Garnica, Olga K., 1977-1978
  - Garvin, Paul L., 1969,1975
    See also Bunker-Ramo Corp.
  - Gearing, Frederick O., 1969
  - Gell, Alfred, 1979
  - Genovese, Eugene D., 1970-1980
  - Ghosh, Samir K., 1971
  - Gibbs, James L., 1970
  - Giglioli, Pier Paolo, 1983
  - Gilbert, Glenn, 1982-1983
  - Giles, Howard, 1973-1974
  - Gilka, Robert G. S. (Jeff), 1979
  - Gill, Sam D., 1975-1981
  - Gilman, Charles, 1978
  - Giroux, Henry A., 1980-1981
  - Glassie, Henry, 1970-1982
  - Gleason, Henry A., 1958-1961,1967-1971,1981
  - Gleason, Jean Berko, 1985
  - Goddard, Ives, 1969-1973,1981
  - Goffman, Erving, 1967-1982
  - Goldstein, Diane, 1986-1987
  - Goldstein, Kenneth S., 1969-1987
  - Golla, Susan, 1983
  - Golla, Victor, 1968,1977-1984
  - Gomes de Matos, Francisco, 1969,1980,1986-1987
  - Goncalves e Silva, Petronilha Beatriz, 1984
  - Goodenough, Ward H., 1958,1960,1970-1986
  - Goodwin, Chuck, 1978-1980
  - Goody, Esther, 1975
  - Gouldner, Alvin, 1974-1978
    See also Theory and Society
  - Gouldner, Helen, 1979
  - Grace, George W., 1963-1966,1978
  - Green, Rayna, 1976-1977,1986
  - Gregersen, Edgar A., 1977,1981
  - Gregorian, Vartan, 1974-1981
  - Greimar, C (?), 1968-1969
  - Grimes, Joseph, 1963-1964
  - Grimshaw, Allen, 1966-1986; 3 folders
    - Folder 1, 1966-1977
    - Folder 2, 1978-1980
    - Folder 3, 1981-1986
  - Grindal, Bruce T., 1974-1976
  - Guirand, Pierre, 1962-1963
  - Guksch, Christian E., 1970,1973
  - Gullahorn, John, 1964
  - Gumperz, John, 1966-1986
  - Gutherie, Grace Pung, 1978-1979
  - Haas, Mary R., 1958-1968,1975,1980
  - Hackney, F. Sheldon, 1981,1983
  - Haida, Yvonne, 1981
  - Hale, Kenneth, 1970-1973,1977-1981,1986
  - Hall, Edward, 1976
  - Halliday, Michael, 1966-1967,1974
  - Hallinan, "Dynamite", 1965-1966
  - Halpin, Marjorie, 1983
  - Hammel, E. A. (Gene), 1963,1972,1985
  - Hancock, Ian, 1968-1983
  - Hanks, William F., 1984
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., 1975-1976
  - Harper & Row, Publishers, 1965-1982
  - Harris, Marvin, 1971,1980
  - Harris, Zellig, 1968,1976
  - Hartman, Hedy, 1975-1978
  - Harvard University Press, 1973-1987
  - Hatton, Howard, 1973-1979
  - Haugen, Einar, 1970,1973
  - Hay, Thomas H., 1978
  - Hays, David G., 1962-1964,1970
  - Heath, Shirley Brice, 1971,1976-1985
  - Hedden, Mark, 1966-1968
  - Heidenheimer, Arnold J., 1984-1985
  - Henry Sweet Society, 1986
  - Herbert, T. Walter, 1983
  - Herman, Ed, 1968
  - Heroy, Babs, 1978
  - Herzog, George, 1959,1975
  - Hess, Thomas, 1979
  - Hickerson, Nancy (Polly), 1970-1982
  - Hill, Clifford A., 1978
  - Hill, Jane H., 1983-1986
  - Hinton, Leanne, 1965-1969,1975-1981
  - Hirsch, Ed, 1976,1979-1980
  - Hiz, Henry T., 1970,1979
  - Hoard, Jim, 1978
  - Hockett, Charles F., 1962,1973
    See also Series II: American Anthropology Association
  - Hoenigswald, Henry M., 1967-1983
  - Hoffman, Daniel, 1976-1980
  - Hogan, Helen, 1969-1972
  - Hoijer, Harry, 1956-1967
  - Holden, Madronna, 1977
  - Holmes, Kris, 1978
    See also Bigelow, Charles
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., 1966-1980
    See also Spindler, George
  - Holt, Robert T., 1965-1970
  - Hooper, Paul, 1973,1976,1978
  - Horowitz, Irving Louis, 1986
  - Householder, Jr., Fred W., 1955,1970,1982
  - Huberman, Leo, 1961,1965
  - Hughes, Thomas, 1985
  - Human Organization, 1982
  - Humphrey, Clifford, 1970
  - Ihm, Peter, 1962-1964
  - Indian Council Fire, 1983-1984
  - Indiana University Press, 1953, 1964-1979; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1953,1964-1971
    - Folder 2, 1972-1979
  - International Journal of American Linguistics, 1960-1965,1980-1986
  - International Social Science Journal, 1971-1972
  - Inverarity, Robert Bruce, 1964-1965
  - Invitations, Acceptances, 1963-1987; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1963-1979
    - Folder 2, 1980-1987
  - Invitations, Declinations, 1966-1987
    - Folder 1, 1966-1979
    - Folder 2, 1980-1987
  - Iowa State University, 1975-1976
  - Irvine, Judith, 1969-1987
  - Istituto Luigi Sturzo, 1969
  - Izumi, Seiichi, 1965
  - Jackson, Bruce, 1987
  - Jacobs, Melville, 1953-1970
  - Jacobsen, William, 1963-1966
  - Jain, Dhanesh K., 1968-1973
  - Jakobson, Roman, 1961-1973,1982-1983
  - Jarrard, Norman E., 1977
  - Jay, Robert, 1972
  - Jeffers, Robert, 1977,1982
  - Jenness, David, 1975-1984
  - Jennings, Jesse, 1963-1964
  - Johannsen, Uwe, 1960-1962,1979-1983
  - John Benjamins Publisher & Bookseller, 1981-1983
  - John Hopkins University, 1974,1978
  - John Hopkins University Press, 1970,1981
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1962,1967-1969,1971
  - John-Steiner, Vera, 1963-1983
  - Johnson, Benedict, 1985
  - Johnston, Francis E., 1985
  - Jones, Bart, 1967-1970,1974, n.d.
  - Jones, Howard Mumford, 1960-1968
  - Jones, Steve, 1983
  - Jones, W. T., 1968,1971
    See also Series II: Wenner-Gren Foundation
  - Joos, Martin, 1968-1969
  - Journal of American Folklore, 1975,1979,1983
    See also Bauman, Richard
  - Journal of Pragmatics, 1975-1981
    See also Mey, Jacob
  - Journal of the History of the Behavioral Sciences, 1963-1986
    See also Stocking, George
    - Folder 1, 1963-1974
    - Folder 2, 1975-1980
    - Folder 3, 1981-1986
  - Juajibioy, Alberto, 1958-1966
  - Juilland, Alphonse, 1975
  - Justice, James, 1980
  - Kac, Michael, 1963-1964
  - Kaldor, Susan, 1965-1978
  - Kalifornsky, Peter & Kari, James, 1979,1984
  - Kang, Shin-pyo, 1981
  - Kaplan, Bonnie, 1968
  - Kartunen, Frances, 1979
  - Katz, Sol, 1983
  - Kaufman, Terrence, 1968-1973
  - Kay, Paul, 1965,1967,1980,1984
  - Keenan, Edward Lewis, 1968-1972, n.d.
  - Keenan, Elinor Ochs, 1968-1984; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1968-1971
    - Folder 2, 1972-1984
  - Kehl, Frank, 1967
  - Kendall, Daythal, 1974-1980
  - Kendall, Martha (Bonnie), 1979,1982
  - Key, Mary Ritchie, 1969,1975,1977
  - Khan, Verity Saifullah, 1979
  - Khubchandani, Lachman M., 1971
  - Kimball, Solon T., 1967-1968
  - Kinkade, M. Dale, 1964,1973,1978-1985
  - Kirshenblatt-Gimblett, Barbara, 1974,1985
  - Kitahara, Michio, 1964
  - Klein, A. Norman, 1965,1969-1976
  - Klein, Jared S., 1977-1978
  - Klein, Sheldon, 1981,1983
  - Kluckhohn, Richard, 1964
  - Knecht, P., 1974-1975
  - Koch, Walter A., 1984
  - Koerner, E. F. Konrad, 1971-1985; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1971-1978
    - Folder 2, 1979-1985
  - Kooij, J. G., 1968
  - Kovtun, Emil, 1960
  - Krader, Lawrence, 1970-1972
  - Kratochvil, Pavel, 1964
  - Krauss, Michael, 1964-1969,1980,1983
  - Kress, Gunther, 1986-1987
  - Kroch, Anthony, 1977,1985-1986
  - Kroeber, A. L. (Alfred Louis) & Theodora, 1959-1972
  - Kroeber, Karl, 1977-1984
  - Kroskrity, Paul, 1984
  - Krueger, John R., 1963
  - Krupat, Arnold, 1985-1987
  - Kuklick, Henrietta, 1981
  - Kuno, S., 1981
  - Kunstadter, Peter, 1964
  - Kurath, Hans, 1981
  - Laboratory of Comparative Human Cognition, 1975-1976
  - Labov, William, 1963-1972, 1974-1987; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1963-1972
    - Folder 2, 1974-1987
  - Lamb, Sydney M., 1962-1977
  - Landar, Herbert, 1963-1966
  - Landsberg, Marge E., 1986
  - Langendoen, D. Terence, 1984
  - Language in Society, 1968-1971
  - Lapoint, Elwyn C., 1983
  - Lavendera, Beatriz, 1972-1987
  - Lawless, Elaine J., 1983
  - Lawton, David, 1968
  - Laycock, D. C., 1968-1969,1978-1979
  - Leach, Edmund, 1965,1970
  - Leap,William, 1973,1977-1979
  - Lee, David, 1981
  - Leeds-Hurwitz, Wendy, 1978-1986
  - Legman, Gershon, 1975,1977,1986
  - LeGuin, Ursula, 1985
  - Leonard, Deni, 1973-1975,1979-1981
  - Leondar, Barbara, 1968
  - Leopold, Joan, 1971-1987
  - Le Page, Robert, 1967-1971
  - Lesser, Alexander, 1965-1966,1972-1973,1981
  - Levine, Robert, 1971-1972
  - Levi-Strauss, Claude, 1961-1968,1977,1986
  - Liberty, Margot, 1975-1976
  - Liljeblad, Sven, 1957
  - Lindenfeld, Jacqueline, 1969,1973,1979-1985
  - Lindig, Wolfgang, 1961
  - Linguistic Association of Canada and the United States, 1975-1976
  - Linguistic Society of America, 1954
  - Linguistics Association of Great Britain, 1971
  - Lisker, Leigh, 1974-1980
  - Lofland, John, 1983
  - Lomax, Alan, 1962,1966,1973
  - Lopez, Barry, 1977
  - Lotz, John, 1965
  - Loudon, Michael, 1983
  - Lounsbury, Floyd G., 1956-1970
  - Lowie, Luella Cole, 1960-1963
  - Lurie, Nancy Oestreich, 1968-1969
  - Lutz, Nancy, 1974
  - Lynton, Ernest A., 1966
  - Macmillan Press Ltd., 1977-1978
  - MacRae, Donald G., 1960-1967
  - Maday, Bela C., 1971
  - Maher, J. Peter, 1975-1983
  - Mair, Heidi L., 1983
  - Malkiel, Yakov, 1958-1974,1984
  - Mandelbaum, David G., 1982,1985
  - Manes, Joan, 1974-1981
  - Mannenbach, Steve, 1975
  - Maquet, Jacques, 1978-1985
  - Marcus, George, 1986
  - Marino, Mary & Kennedy, Kenneth, 1962-1971
  - Markey, Thomas L., 1979,1983
  - Martin, Paul S., 1962-1964
  - Martin, Sam, 1965-1966
  - Martin, Tom & Anne, 1979-1980
  - Mathiot, Madeleine, 1966
  - Matthews, P. H., 1986
  - Mattina, Anthony, 1983
  - Matossian, Lou Ann, 1986
  - Maud, Ralph, 1979-1987
  - Maynard, Kent, 1985
  - Mazlish, Bruce, 1977
  - McAllester, David, 1965,1980
  - McAllister, Gilbert, 1963
  - McConnell-Ginet, Sally, 1983
  - McDermott, Ray, 1977-1986
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1965
  - McHugh, Joseph, 1965
  - McLendon, Sally, 1976-1981
  - McLeod, Norma, 1966
  - McQuown, Norman, 1965
  - Mead, Margaret, 1977-1983
    See also Series II: American Anthropology Association, Thailand Committee
  - Mehan, Hugh (Bud), 1975-1983
  - Merritt, Marilyn, 1969-1984
  - Messenger, John, 1976
  - Mey, Jacob L., 1975-1986
    See also Journal of Pragmatics
  - Meyerson, Martin, 1971,1979
  - Michaels, Sarah, 1982-1983
  - Miki, Etsuzo, 1983
  - Milke, Wilhelm, 1961-1966
  - Miller, Elmer, 1972
  - Miller, Wick, 1964-1970,1975
  - Miner, Kenneth L., 1982
  - Minoff, Iles & Karen, 1972-1976
  - Mintz, Sidney, 1960-1985; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1960-1971
    - Folder 2, 1972-1985
  - Mithun, Marianne, 1983
  - Moberg, George, 1965-1966
  - Molina, Felipe S.& Evers, Larry, 1982,1987
  - Moore, Ralph, 1984
  - Morin, Alexander J., 1965
  - Mostny, Greta, 1961
  - Mouton Publishers, 1962-1982; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1962-1965
    - Folder 2, 1966-1982
  - Murphy, Bill, 1980-1982
  - Murphy, Robert F., 1965,1971
  - Murra, Laura, 1968-1976
  - Murray, Stephen, 1976-1987
  - Nader, Laura, 1965,1970-1980
  - Nash, June, 1966,1968
  - The Nation, 1968,1976,1980,1984
  - National Dissemination & Assessment Center, 1977-1978
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1970-1981
  - National Institute of Mental Health, 1966-1972
  - National Science Foundation, 1961-1964,1971-1974,1980-1981
  - Navajo Community College, 1981-1982
  - Needham, Joseph, 1968
  - Needham, Rodney, 1968,1975
  - Needham, Roger, 1962-1964
  - Nelson, Cynthia, 1966
  - Neustupny, Jiri, 1965-1969,1978,1984-1986
  - Newbury House Publishers, Inc., 1980-1981
  - Newman, Roger, 1970-1972
  - Newman, Stanley, 1962-1966
  - Newmeyer, Fritz, 1983
  - New Society, 1966,1968-1969
  - Nguyen, Dinh-Hoa, 1977
  - Nichols, Patricia C., 1975-1976
  - Nida, Eugene A., 1964-1986
  - Nine-Curt, Carmen Judith, 1976
  - Nixon, Lee Goldblatt, 1969-1977
  - Noricks, Jay, 1981
  - Northwest Regional Education Laboratory, 1980-1981
  - Norwegian Archaeological Review, 1969-1971
  - Noy, Dov, 1983
  - Nussenbaum, Gladys, 1976
  - Nutini, Hugo G. & Buchler, Ira R., 1967-1968
  - O'Barr, William M., 1985-1987
  - Odyssey, 1979-1980
  - Oghu, John U., 1979-1980
  - Ohio University Press, 1983
  - Ohl, Ronald E., 1980
  - Olmsted, D. L., 1963-1976
  - O'Neil, Wayne, 1986
  - Orbell, Margaret, 1978-1979
  - Ormsby-Lennon, Hugh, 1975-1981
  - Ortiz, Alfonso, 1968-1981
  - Ortiz, Manuel, 1976
  - Osgood, Cornelius, 1970
  - Oswalt, Bob, 1966,1979,1981
  - Owen, Roger C., 1965
  - Owusu, Maxwell, 1978
  - Oxford University Press, 1978
  - Pages, Robert, 1961-1964
  - Palson, Chuck, 1970,1972, n.d.
  - Pantheon Books, 1968-1974,1980-1982
  - Paradigm Press, 1986
  - Parsons, Talcott, 1959
  - Pateman, Trevor, 1981
  - Paul F. Lazarsfeld Fund, 1978-1981
  - Peacock, James L., 1966-1969,1974-1977
  - Pedersen, Karen, 1982
  - Pelto, Pertti J. (Bert), 1965,1967
  - Peng, Fred C. C., 1965,1975
  - Pennsylvania State University Press, 1975
  - Percival, W. Keith, 1970,1977,1981
  - Perlman, Melvin L., 1968-1969
  - Perlmutter, David M., 1970
  - Perry, Barbara, 1976
  - Persson, Lars, 1970,1972
  - Peter de Ridder Press, 1974,1978
  - Philips, Susan, 1967-1984; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1967-1969
    - Folder 2, 1970-1984
  - Piault, Colette, 1963-1971,1980
  - Pierce, Joe E., 1963-1968
  - Pike, Kenneth L., 1955-1971,1980
  - Pinnow, Heinz-Jurgen, 1964-1969,1976
  - Pinxten, Rik, 1974,1985-1986
  - Pitkin, Harvey, 1973,1978-1979
  - Pittman, Dick and Kay, 1978,1983
  - Poirier, Charline, 1986
  - Pollard, Velma, 1980
  - Polomè, Edgar C., 1967-1970,1976,1979
  - Powers, William K., 1965-1970
  - Praeger, 1979
  - Prattis, Iain, 1982-1986
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1970,1977
  - Preston, Dennis, 1981,1986
  - Preston, Richard, 1983-1984
  - Prewitt, Kenneth, 1983
  - Price, Richard & Sally, 1977-1980,1986
  - Pride, John, 1969,1974-1984
  - Prince, Ellen, 1975-1981
  - Prince, Gerald, 1974
  - Princeton University, 1969-1975
  - Quasha, George, 1968
  - Queens College of the City University of New York, 1986
  - Radway, Jan, 1984
  - Ramasubramanian, N., 1965
  - Ramsey, Jarold, 1970-1987; 3 folders
    - Folder 1, 1970-1973
    - Folder 2, 1974-1979
    - Folder 3, 1980-1987
  - Randolph, Richard, 1964,1966
  - Rayman, Gyanchand, 1979
  - Read, Allen Walker, 1964
  - Reichert, Josh, 1975-1977
  - Reina, Ruben E., 1968,1971
  - Reinecke, John E., 1967-1971,1979
  - Reisman, Karl, 1960-1983
  - Renjilian, Debbie & JaneYoung, 1978
  - Renner, Egon, 1986
  - Requests for Reprints by Hymes, 1957-1987; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1957-1980
    - Folder 2, 1981-1987
  - Requests for Reprints by Others, 1954-1986, n.d.; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1954-1976
    - Folder 2, 1977-1986, n.d.
  - Research Center for the Language Sciences, 1970,1972
    See also Koerner, E. F. Konrad
  - Research in Social Policy, 1985
  - Rey, Alain, 1971
  - Richardson, Irvine, 1968
  - Rickford, John R., 1971-1987
  - Rieff, Philip, 1967-1972
  - Riesman, David, 1961-1979
  - Rigsby, Bruce, 1963-1984
  - Ringe, Donald, 1985-1987
  - Ringle, Martin, 1981
  - Ripley, Sue, 1962
  - Roberts, John M., 1965-1971
  - Robinson, Sandra, 1979
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1977
  - Roe, Peter G., 1983
  - Rohner, Ronald P., 1966
  - Romaine, Suzanne, 1982,1985
  - Romano, Al, 1974-1977
  - Romney, A. Kimball, 1963-1964,1966
  - Rona, José Pedro, 1966-1967
  - Rosaldo, Renato, 1981
  - Rosen, Harold, 1984-1986
  - Rosenberg, Jerome L., 1981
  - Ross, John (Haj), 1968,1981
  - Roszak, Theodore, 1968
  - Rowe, John H., 1963-1967
  - Rubinstein, Robert A., 1978-1983
  - Ruby, Jay, 1976-1980
  - Ruoff, A. LaVonne, 1978-1985
  - Ruprecht, Hans-George, 1982-1983
  - Rutgers University Press, 1979
  - Sacharoff, Mary, 1984
  - Sackett, S. J., 1963
  - Sage Publications, Inc., 1986
  - Salmon, Vivian, 1964,1976,1986
  - Salmond, Anne Thorpe, 1970-1983
  - Samarin, William J., 1966-1970,1981
  - Sampson, Geoffrey, 1979
  - Sanday, Peggy, 1977-1979,1985
  - San Francisco Oracle, 1967
  - Sankoff, Gillian, 1969-1985
  - Sansom, Basil L., 1980
  - Sapir, J. David, 1958-1987; 3 folders
    - Folder 1, 1958-1970
    - Folder 2, 1971-1979
    - Folder 3, 1980-1987
  - Sapir, Philip, 1974-1986; 3 folders
    - Folder 1, 1974-1983
    - Folder 2, January-April,1984
    - Folder 3, May-June,1984,1985-1986
  - Sarana, Gopala, 1967
  - Sarles, Harvey, 1967
  - Sather, Clifford, 1967
  - Saugstad, Per, 1982
  - Saville-Troike, Muriel, 1980-1985
  - Scargill, M. H., 1968
  - Schegloff, Emanuel A., 1967
  - Schieffelin, Bambi, 1977-1979, n.d.
  - Schlichter, Alice, 1981
  - Schneider, David M., 1958-1975
  - Scholte, Bob, 1963-1979; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1963-1968
    - Folder 2, 1969-1979
  - School of Oriental and African Studies, 1972-1973
  - Schroyer, Trent, 1970-1972
  - Science, 1969,1978
  - Scollon, Ronald, 1980
  - Scur, G. S., 1965-1969
  - Sebeok, Thomas A., 1955-1982
    See also Current Trends in Linguistics
  - Service, Elman, 1960
  - Shaffer, E.S., 1984-1985
  - Sharp, Lynda, 1978
  - Sherzer, Joel, 1968-1987; 3 folders
    - Folder 1, 1968-1972
    - Folder 2, 1973-1979
    - Folder 3, 1980-1987
  - Shevoroshkin, V., 1980-1982
  - Shimanoff, Susan B., 1979
  - Shipley, William, 1965,1970
  - Shuy, Roger W., 1968,1975,1980,1985
  - Sibley, Elbridge, 1966-1968
  - Sigman, Stuart, 1978
  - Silver, Shirley, 1977,1981
  - Silverman, Martin, 1961-1969
  - Silverman, Sydel, 1967
  - Silverstein, Michael, 1966-1986; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1966-1972
    - Folder 2, 1973-1986
  - Silverstein, Raymond, 1967,1974-1977
  - Singer, Eliot, 1983
  - Singer, Jerome E., 1966
  - The Sixties Press, 1966
  - Skinner, Quentin, 1970
  - Slobodin, Richard, 1965,1967
  - Smalley, William A., 1972-1973
  - Smith, Allan H., 1965,1968,1970
  - Smith, Barbara Herrnstein, 1966,1977,1983
  - Smith, Daniel L., 1983-1984
  - Smith, Elizabeth Leigh, 1975
  - Smith, Ian, 1979
  - Smith, Kenneth D., 1968-1970
  - Smith, Nelson J., 1969
  - Smitherman, Geneva, 1979-1981,1985
  - Snyder, Gary, 1951-1958, 1966-1975,1982, n.d.; 3 folders
    - Folder 1, 1951-1952
      - "Summer Solstice & and Miserable Modern Man," and "Songs for a Four-Crowned Dancing Hat.", 1951 April 30
    - Folder 2, 1953-1958
    - Folder 3, 1966-1975,1982, n.d.
  - Social Sciences & Human Research Council of Canada, 1986
  - Society for Social Responsibility in Science, 1965
  - Solomon, Richard, 1956
  - Southworth, Franklin C., 1967-1969
  - Speth, William, 1979-1981
  - Spicer, Edward H., 1962-1963,1965
  - Spindler, George D., 1965-1970
    See also Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc.
  - Sprauve, Gilbert A., 1979-1980
  - Stafford, William, 1977-1978
  - Stanford University Press, 1980
  - Stankiewicz, Edward, 1969-1970
  - Steele, Susan, 1980-1981
  - Stein, Jonathan M., 1973
  - Steinberg, Danny D., 1968
  - Steiner, Peter, 1982-1983
  - Stellar, Eliot, 1977-1978
  - Stephens, William, 1970
  - Stern, Theodore, 1972,1983
  - Stewart, S. A., n.d.
  - Stocking, George W., 1966-1986; 2 folders
    See also Journal of the History of the Behavioral Sciences
    - Folder 1, 1966-1979
    - Folder 2, 1980-1986
  - Stouffer, Samuel A., 1958-1959
  - Sturtevant, William C., 1956-1985; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1956-1969
    - Folder 2, 1970-1985
  - Summer Institute of Linguistics, 1963-1964,1969,1980-1981
  - Suttles, Wayne, 1967,1976
  - Swadesh, Morris, 1954-1960
  - Swadesh, Morris & Evangelina, 1961-1976
  - Swanton, John R., 1956-1957,1962
  - Swiggers, Pierre, 1980-1985
  - Szwed, John F., 1965-1981
  - Tannen, Deborah, 1980-1986
  - Tanner, Nancy, 1963-1967
  - Tavistock Publications Ltd., 1977-1983
  - Tax, Sol, 1954,1965,1968
  - Taylor, Douglas, 1953-1962,1967-1977
  - Teachers College Press, 1967,1971-1986
  - Tedlock, Dennis, 1967-1987; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1967-1979
    - Folder 2, 1980-1987
  - Teeter, Karl V., 1961-1979,1984
  - Tentchoff, Dorice, 1973-1975
  - Textor, Robert, 1963
  - Thackray, Arnold, 1972-1974,1982-1986
  - Thayer, Lee, 1965,1986, n.d.
  - Theory and Society, 1974-1985
  - Thomason, Sally, 1981-1986
  - Thompson, George W., 1974
  - Thompson, Laurence C., 1963,1971,1977,1981-1982
  - Thompson, Stith, 1955,1961
  - Thoresen, Timothy, 1971,1974
  - Thorne, Barrie, 1976
  - Thorne, James Peter, 1966
  - Thorpe, Maner, 1960-1966
  - Tiwary, K. M., 1970,1980
  - Toelken, Barre, 1973-1982
  - Tonkin, Elizabeth, 1969
  - Tonkin, Humphrey, 1979,1984,1986
  - Trager, George L., 1958,1963-1966,1973-1974
  - Trans-action, 1969
  - Traugott, Elizabeth, 1972-1973,1979,1982
  - Tripp, Sue, 1966-1967,1970-1974
  - Troike, Rudolph C., 1962,1968,1975-1979
  - Tsuzaki, Stanley, 1967-1970
  - Tyler, Stephen A., 1967,1970,1984
  - United Indians of All Tribes Foundation, 1979
  - University of Arizona Press, 1983-1986
  - University of British Columbia Press, 1984-1985
  - University of California-Berkeley
    - Academic Senate, 1966
    - Dept. of Anthropology, 1963-1965,1986
  - University of California Press, 1963,1974,1978,1981,1986
  - University of Illinois Press, 1977-1978,1986
  - University of Maryland, 1981
  - University of Massachusetts Press, 1981
  - University of Melbourne, 1974-1975
  - University of Nebraska Press, 1980-1986
  - University of New Mexico-The Graduate School-College of Education, 1977
  - University of Oklahoma Press, 1985-1986
  - University of Pennsylvania
    - Annenberg School of Communication, 1978-1979,1982-1984
    - Center for Urban Ethnography, 1968-1971
    - Department of Anthropology, 1964-1986
    - Department of Folklore & Folklife, 1967-1985; 3 folders
      - Folder 1, 1967-1978
      - Folder 2, 1979-1981
      - Folder 3, 1982-1985
    - Department of History, 1974, n.d.
    - Department of Linguistics, 1970-1987; 3 folders
      - Folder 1, 1970-1976
      - Folder 2, 1977-1980
      - Folder 3, 1981-1987
    - Department of Sociology, 1973-1975,1982
    - Faculty Senate, 1973-1975
    - Graduate School of Education, 1969-1986
    - Prospective Students, 1970-1976
    - University Museum, 1965-1972,1980
    - Various Departments, 1965-1987, n.d.
  - University of Pennsylvania Press, 1969-1987; 5 folders
    - Folder 1, 1969-1981
    - Folder 2, 1982
    - Folder 3, 1983
    - Folder 4, 1984-1985
    - Folder 5, 1986-1987
  - University of St. Andrews, 1981
  - University of Southern California-Center for Humanities, 1979
  - University of Tennessee Press, 1974
  - University of Texas Press, 1976-1984
  - University of Washington, 1984
  - University of Washington Press, 1973-1975,1981-1982
  - University of Western Australia, 1981-1982
  - Urciuoli, Bonnie, 1987
  - Valdman, Albert, 1967-1968,1980-1985
  - Valory, Dale, 1966
  - Van Arsdale, Minor, 1963-1964
  - Van de Craen, Pete, 1980-1983
  - Van Dijk, Teun A., 1979-1983
  - Van Horn, Lawrence F., 1981
  - Van Ness, Christine, 1982,1986
  - Van Valin, Robert, 1980
  - Vargas-Baron, Emily, 1972
  - Vazquez, Juan Adolfo, 1984-1985
  - Verburg, Pieter A. and Cees Arjen, 1965-1971, n.d.
  - Voegelin, C. F. & F. M., 1955-1981; 2 folders
    See also International Journal of American Linguistics
    - Folder 1, 1955-1964
    - Folder 2, 1965-1981
  - Vogt, Evon Z., 1957-1968,1983
  - Voorhoeve, Jan, 1966-1970
  - Vorlat, Emma, 1971
  - Wagley, Charles, 1971,1980
  - Wagner, Roy, 1977
  - Wallace, Anthony F. C., 1961-1971,1980,1986
  - Walter de Gruyter & Co., 1981
  - Wang, Hahn-Sok, 1980-1981
  - Ward, Robert E., 1970
  - Wasson, George, 1977-1978
  - Waterhouse, Lynn, 1973-1981
  - Waugh, Linda R., 1986
  - Waveland Press, Inc., 1984
  - Weber, Rose-Marie, 1975
  - Weinreich, Uriel, 1955,1963-1964
  - Welbon, Guy, 1986
  - Welkenhuyzen, Lucien, 1967
  - Wells, Rulon, 1982
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anthropology, 1962,1965
  - Werner, Oswald, 1962-1967
  - Wescott, R. W., 1982,1985
  - Wesleyan University Press, 1978
  - West, Frank, 1966-1967
  - Westermann, Rudolf, 1965
  - Whalen, Philip, 1965
  - Whinnom, Keith, 1967-1970
  - Whistler, Kenneth, 1977-1984